Abbot-Charnay Photograph Collection 1859-1882 Mss.913.72.Ab23
American Philosophical Society
- Abbot-Charnay Photograph Collection (Box 1-2)
  - Quien sabe [portrait of woman], Valparaiso, Chile, ca.1880; 115; Carte de visite; Establecimiento fotografico
  - [Portrait of woman], Valparaiso, Chile, ca.1880; 116; Carte de visite; Establecimiento fotografico
  - Miss Turnbill [portrait of woman], Valparaiso, Chile, ca.1880; 117; Carte de visite; Establecimiento fotografico
  - [Portrait of woman], Valparaiso, Chile, ca.1880; 118; Carte de visite; Establecimiento fotografico
  - [Portrait of woman], Lima, Peru, ca.1880; 119; Carte de visite; Courret, E.
  - [Portrait of woman], Lima, Peru, ca.1880; 120; Carte de visite; Courret, E.
  - [Portrait of woman], Valparaiso, Chile, ca.1880; 121; Carte de visite; Establecimiento fotografico
  - [Portrait of woman], Lima, Peru, ca.1880; 122; Carte de visite; Courret, E.
  - Rose Sauri, [Portrait of woman], Lima, Peru, ca.1880; 123; Carte de visite; Courret, E.
  - Feunchal natives, Madeira, 1864; 124; Carte de visite; Camacho, J. F.